China Subject Files, Inclusive: 1937-2018, undated, Bulk: 1961-1992
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General, 1937-2018, undated; 1
  - International Relations. Chinese Diplomacy, 1967-1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - International Relations. Chinese Diplomatic Missions, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - International Relations. Sino-German Relations, 1966-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - International Relations. Sino-Romanian Relations, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - International Relations. Sino-Czech Relations, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Relations. Sino-Polish Relations, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Relations. China in Africa, 1963-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Relations. China in East Europe, 1973-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Relations. Sino-Albanian Relations, 1977-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - International Relations. Sino-Yugoslavian Relations, 1974-1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - International Relations. Sino-Spanish Relations, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - International Relations. China-Greek Relations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - International Relations. Sino-Italian Relations, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - International Relations. Chinese Relations with West Europe, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - International Relations. Sino-Dutch Relations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Relations. Sino-Belgian Relations, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Relations. Sino-French Relations, 1974-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Relations. Sino-Japanese Relations, 1971-1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Relations. Sino-Pakistani-Indian Relations, 1964-1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - International Relations. Sino-Palestinian-Israeli Relations, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - International Relations. China in Southeast Asia, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - International Relations. Sino- Afghani Relations, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International Relations. Sino-Persian Relations, 1978-1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - International Relations. Sino- Cambodian Relations, 1970-1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - International Relations. Sino-Indonesian, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - International Relations. Sino-Korean Relations, 1978-1993 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - International Relations. Sino-Arab Relations, 1970-1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - International Relations. Sino-Mongolian Relations, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - International Relations. Sino-Vietnamese Relations, 1965-1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - International Relations. Sino-Taiwanese Relations, 1970-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - International Relations. Transfer of Hong Kong to China, 1977-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - International Relations. Hong Kong General, 1956-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - International Relations. Sino-British Relations, 1965-1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - International Relations. Queen's Visit to China, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - International Relations. Chinese Acquisition of Macau, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Post Mao Changes in China, 1976-1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Post Mao Social and Economic Changes in China, 1977-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Post Mao Changes. Gang of Four, 1976-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Post Cultural Revolution Changes. Cultural Revival After Gang of Four, 1965- 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Post Mao Changes in China Book Reviews, 1976- 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Western Reactions to Changes, 1973-2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Bernard Levin Thoughts on Changes, 1977-2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. Conference on the History of the Republic of China, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Post-Cultural Revolution Changes. "Black Country Girl, in Red Country" Book Review, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Educational Services Exchange with China, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Women in China, 1975-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Youths, 1969-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Abuse of Orphans, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Abuse of Orphans. Birth Control Policies in China. One Child Policy, 1963-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Society, Family, Sociology (1 of 2), 1961-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Society, Family, Sociology (2 of 2), 1972-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Sports in China, 1971-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Family, Education, and Youth in China. Education, 1961-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Party and Communism. China's Bureaucracy, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Party and Communism. Review of Chinese Communism, 1974-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Party and Communism. Ideology (1 of 2), 1975-1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Party and Communism. Ideology (2 of 2), 1962-1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Party and Communism. History of the Party (1 of 3), 1966-1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Party and Communism. History of the Party (2 of 3), 1964-1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Party and Communism. History of the Party (3 of 3), 1958-1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. A study of the Chinese Language Christian Broadcasting Programs Final Report, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Literature, 1945-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Chinese Newspapers, 1965-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Chinese Play Script, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Movies by Chinese Film Makers, 1986-1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Entertainment and Media in China, 1961-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Censorship of Media, 1977-1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Unofficial Media and Literature, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Conference of the National Association of Unofficial Magazines, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. China Today News, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Arts and Music, 1966-1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Gospel Radio for China, 1983-1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Western Media in China, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Media, Arts, and Literature. Western Broadcasts in China, 1965-1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Lifetime Employment in China, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Transition to Market Economy and Quality of Life, 1986-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Anti-Corruption Campaign, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Chinese City Life, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Land Reform in China, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Economy (1 of 2), 1982-1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Economy (2 of 2), 1970-1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Agriculture and Labor, 1961-1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Modern Chinese Economic Practices, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Chinese Village Life and Practices, 1974-1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Alternative Energy in China, 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Chinese Hospitals and Medicine, 1968-1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Economics, City and Country Life. Black Market Organs, 1990-1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Student Led Demonstrations and Protests, 1981-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Chinese University Students, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Public Demonstrations, Protests and Uprisings, 1968-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Race Riots in China, 1979-1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Posters for Democracy and Democracy Wall, 1975-1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Terrorism, 1978-1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Social Unrest and Chinese Response. Hijackings in China, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Political Dissidents. Fang Lizhi, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Political Dissidents. Han Dongang, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Political Dissidents. Wang Dan, 1989-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Political Dissidents. Harry Wu, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Political Dissidents. Lia Gang, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Political Dissidents. Wang Juntao, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Political Dissidents. Jiang Qisheng, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Political Dissidents. Zhai Weimin, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Political Dissidents. Chen Yun, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Political Dissidents. Liu Binyan, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Political Dissidents. Ting Ling, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Political Dissidents. Xu Wenli, 1982-1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Political Dissidents. Bai Hua, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Political Dissidents. Liu Qing, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Political Dissidents. Wei Jinasheng, 1979-1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Political Dissidents. Political Dissidents. General, 1974-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Political Dissidents. Arrests and Imprisonments of Political Dissidents, 1979-1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Political Dissidents. "Prisoner of Mao" Book Review, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Political Dissidents. Persecution of Intellectuals, 1986-1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Political Dissidents. Political Rehabilitations, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Political Dissidents. Amnesty International, 1978-1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Chinese Constitution, 1975-1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Human Rights in China. General, 1973-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Religion and Law: Human Rights Watch, 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Legal Codes and the Courts, 1965-1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Crime in China, 1976-1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Executions, 1966-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Violence by Red Guards, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Chinese Secret Service, 1977-1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Civil Aviation Administration of China, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Chinese National Police Force, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Torture in China, 1978-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Political Psychiatry, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Prisoner of War Camps in China, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Thought Reform in a Chinese Prison Report, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Chinese Prison System, 1974-1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - The Law, the Courts, Prisons, and Rights. Prison Labor, 1980-1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Chinese Alphabet, 1979-undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Archeology in China, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Selected Bibliographies, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Human Trafficking in China, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Bomb and Air Raid Shelter, 1972-1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Report in French. Problemes Politiques Et Sociaux Reports, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Emails and Press Releases from Keston, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Visual Materials, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. Reviews on Books about China, 1965-1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Collection. International travel for Chinese Nationals, 1978-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Expats in China, 1972-1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Foreign Missionaries in China, 1966-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Foreign Tourism in China, 1963-1982, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Segregation of Foreigners in China, 1965-1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Chinese Marriages to Foreigners, 1977-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Foreign Detainees in China, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Natural Disasters. Foreign Aid, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Visits of Christians to China, 1975-1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Archbishop Visit to China, 1983-1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Visits from Secular Organizations and Individuals, 1963-1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Foreigners in China. Religious and Secular. Visits from Christian Leaders to China, 1964-1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Religion in China. General (1 of 14), 1958-1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Religion in China. General (2 of 14), 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Religion in China. General (3 of 14), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Religion in China. General (4 of 14), 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Religion in China. General (5 of 14), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Religion in China. General (6 of 14), 1990 January-July (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Religion in China. General (7 of 14), 1990 August-December (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Religion in China. General (8 of 14), 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Religion in China. General (9 of 14), 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Religion in China. General (10 of 14), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Religion in China. General (11 of 14), 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Religion in China. General (12 of 14), 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Religion in China. General (13 of 14), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Religion in China. General (14 of 14), Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Statistics on Church Persecution, 1972-1998, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Religious Persecution General, 1966-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Religious Prisoners, 1963-1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Chinese Christian Martyrs, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Watchman Knee, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Christians Against Torture, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Religious Literature, 1970-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. House Church in China, 1980-1990, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Three-Self Patriotic Movement Persecution of House Churches, 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Reversal of Chinese Persecution on Religion, 1962-1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. China Reopens Churches, 1978-1988, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Revival Church Growth, 1979-2001, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. Religious Theology, 1978-1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Bibles (1 of 2), 1952-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Bibles (2 of 2), 1948-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Religion and Law (1 of 3), 1937-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Religion and Law (2 of 3), 1985-1993, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Religion and Law (3 of 3), 1951-1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Chinese Research on Religion, 1960-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Bible Smuggling and Open Arms, 1975-1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Amity Foundation in China, 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Atheism in China, 1964-1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Denominations and Sects. Religious Sects and Cults, 1986-2002 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Denominations and Sects. Folk Religion and Witches in China, 1976-1986 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Denominations and Sects. Falun Gong in China, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Clippings from China Reporting Services, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Clippings from China Reporting Services, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Denominational, 1964-2003, undated; 2
  The Denominational series contains materials related to specific Christian denominations, including Protestants, Catholics, Lutherans, Methodists, Presbyterians, Mennonites, Seventh Day Adventists, and Orthodox, as well as Judaism, Buddhism, Tibetan Buddhism (Lamaism), Confucianism, and Daoism.
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (1 of 21), 1960-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (2 of 21), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (3 of 21), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (4 of 21), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (5 of 21), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (6 of 21), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (7 of 21), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (8 of 21), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (9 of 21), 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (10 of 21), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (11 of 21), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (12 of 21), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (13 of 21), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (14 of 21), 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (15 of 21), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (16 of 21), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (17 of 21), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (18 of 21), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (19 of 21), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (20 of 21), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. General (21 of 21), 1994-2001, 2018 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. Roman Catholic Priest Letter, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. Ordination of Bishops, 1981-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in China. Roman Catholic Visits to China, 1984-1993 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Protestant Church in China. The Three-Self Church, 1981-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Protestant Church in China. Chinese Christian Visits to the West, 1981-1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Protestant Church in China. Taiwan, 1975-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Protestant Church in China. Hong Kong, 1980-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Protestant Church in China. Dr. Jonathan Chao on Christianity in China, 1975-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Protestant Church in China. Open Letters, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Protestant Church in China. Western Reactions, 1964-1998, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Protestant Church in China. Contacts with the West, 1977-1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Protestant Church in China. Reports from Chinese Church Research Center, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Protestant Church in China. Christian Theological Seminaries, 1980-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Protestant Church in China. Reports and Studies on Christianity in China, 1978-1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Protestant Church in China. Religious Response to Tiananmen Square Massacre, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Protestant Church in China. Evangelical Approach to the Church in China, 1975-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Protestant Church in China. Report on Church Community Workers Study Tour, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Protestant Church in China. Christian China Study Group Meetings, 1971-1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Protestant Church in China. Christian Conferences, 1978-1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Protestant Church in China. Chinese Church Oversees, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Protestant Church in China. Christian Charity Work in China, 1981-1993 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Religious Persecution and the House Church. OMF China Prayer Reports, 1993-1998 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bibles, Religion, and Religious Law in China. Daoism in China, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Denominations and Sects. Jews in China, 1986-2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Denominations and Sects. Mennonites in China, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Denominations and Sects. Lutheranism in China, 1989-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Denominations and Sects. Orthodoxy in China, 1967-1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Denominations and Sects. Islam in China, 1965-1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Denominations and Sects. Confucianism, 1965-1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Denominations and Sects. Presbyterian Church in China, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Denominations and Sects. Seventh Day Adventists in China, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Denominations and Sects. Buddhism in China, 1964- 1989 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Denominations and Sects. Buddhism in Tibet, 1972-1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Denominations and Sects. Lamaism in China, 1973-2001 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Denominations and Sects. Buddhist Samizdat, 1884-1986 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Denominations and Sects. Methodist Church in China, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Denominations and Sects. Lutheran Theological Reflection on the China Study, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Denominations and Sects. Lutheran News, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Denominations and Sects. Panchen Lama in Tibet, 1965-1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)